Have an Idea for a New Product or Invention?

Have an Idea for a New Product or Invention?

##### Errors

×

Close

Loading...

Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy: Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Invention companies websites. You can visit Invention companies websites without revealing any personal information. However, we do require certain personal information if you wish to register for a members account, receive newsletters, or to receive a quote for moving related services. On some pages, you can request to be contacted for the purpose of responding to questions, comments or information relating to our website and/or services. On some pages, you can register with our website if you would like to receive free quotes from our certified partners. The information you submit via the online quote form will not be used for any purpose unless you complete the registration form.

The Way We Use Information: We use the information you provide about yourself and/or your company to respond to your questions and/or comments to send to our certified partners to request free quotes, and also to share with our third party marketing partners so they may send you offers for goods and services which you may find of interest. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with our affiliates/advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited our website, or that Y number of individuals clicked on an advertiser's banner or link. If you would like to unsubscribe from the site you may opt out here [Unsubscribe](https://secure-site.net/unsubscribe) or write to us at: 200 Broad Hollow Road. Melville, NY 11747

Our Commitment to Data Security: To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy: Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Our Service Mark Information: Invention companies.com are Service Marks of Invention companies. All content, graphics and code included in the electronic web pages of Invention companies, are the exclusive ownership of Invention companies, All rights reserved. No part of Invention companies websites may be reproduced in any way or by any means, including print and electronic, without the prior written permission of Invention companies. The information provided herein may not be used to construct any mailing list, to create any promotional materials, to create any links, or for any other commercial purpose without the prior expressed written permission of Invention companies.

Use Of Invention companies Websites: Use of Invention companies websites are offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein. Your use of this website constitutes your agreement to all of the Terms and Conditions of Use. This website contains links to other web pages and websites operated either by Invention companies or Third Parties. Use of this website is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use as contained herein. You agree to review and abide by the Terms and Conditions of Use contained herein. If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this statement, please do not provide any personal information.

Our Terms And Conditions Of Use: This website is for your personal and non-commercial use. Except as expressly agreed herein, you may not display, reproduce, copy, modify, license, sell or disseminate in any manner any information obtained from this website. This website may contain inaccurate or incorrect information. Invention companies may make modifications to the content presented on this website at any time without notice. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and Invention companies as a result of use of this website or the existence of the Terms and Conditions of Use. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. Invention companies reserves the right to revise the Terms and Conditions and/or Privacy Policy at any time without notice by updating this posting. Use of any information or data provided by this website, without prior written permission by Invention companies, is expressly prohibited and may result in civil and/or criminal action. Violators will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible. Under no circumstances will Invention companies be liable for any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use or data, whether in an action of contract or in connection with the use or performance of information available from this website. Any action related to this website will be governed by Arizona law and controlling U.S. federal law. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Maricopa County, Arizona for all disputes arising out of or relating to this website.

Third Party Websites: This website contains links to other Third Party websites, which are not operated by Invention companies. These Third Party websites are not under the control of Invention companies and Invention companies is not responsible for the contents of any linked Third Party website or any link contained in a Third Party website. Invention companies provides these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Invention companies.

Disclaimer: The data that is provided by Invention companies is intended solely for informational purposes. Invention companies does not necessarily endorse or support any data provided by its affiliates/advertisers. Any products or services offered or sold by Invention companies affiliates/advertisers are the sole responsibility of the affiliates/advertisers and are not offered or supported by Invention companies. As Invention companies websites are solely an information resource, Invention companies is not responsible for the actual quality of any product or service offered by any iRelocation Network affiliates/advertisers that is received, including any expressed or implied warranties offered by such affiliates/advertisers. It is the individual customer's complete responsibility and obligation to independently assess the quality of any services or products that they purchase, and to make sure that these services or products meet the individual's needs. Users agree that Invention companies is not liable in any way for any damages that may occur from the use of current or former member's products or services, or for any errors or omissions that may appear on the Invention companies websites.

Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy: Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Invention companies websites. You can visit Invention companies websites without revealing any personal information. However, we do require certain personal information if you wish to register for a members account, receive newsletters, or to receive a quote for moving related services. On some pages, you can request to be contacted for the purpose of responding to questions, comments or information relating to our website and/or services. On some pages, you can register with our website if you would like to receive free quotes from our certified partners. The information you submit via the online quote form will not be used for any purpose unless you complete the registration form.

The Way We Use Information: We use the information you provide about yourself and/or your company to respond to your questions and/or comments to send to our certified partners to request free quotes, and also to share with our third party marketing partners so they may send you offers for goods and services which you may find of interest. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with our affiliates/advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited our website, or that Y number of individuals clicked on an advertiser's banner or link. If you would like to unsubscribe from the site you may opt out here [Unsubscribe](https://secure-site.net/unsubscribe) or write to us at: 200 Broad Hollow Road. Melville, NY 11747

Our Commitment to Data Security: To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy: Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Our Service Mark Information: Invention companies.com are Service Marks of Invention companies. All content, graphics and code included in the electronic web pages of Invention companies, are the exclusive ownership of Invention companies, All rights reserved. No part of Invention companies websites may be reproduced in any way or by any means, including print and electronic, without the prior written permission of Invention companies. The information provided herein may not be used to construct any mailing list, to create any promotional materials, to create any links, or for any other commercial purpose without the prior expressed written permission of Invention companies.

Use Of Invention companies Websites: Use of Invention companies websites are offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein. Your use of this website constitutes your agreement to all of the Terms and Conditions of Use. This website contains links to other web pages and websites operated either by Invention companies or Third Parties. Use of this website is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use as contained herein. You agree to review and abide by the Terms and Conditions of Use contained herein. If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this statement, please do not provide any personal information.

Our Terms And Conditions Of Use: This website is for your personal and non-commercial use. Except as expressly agreed herein, you may not display, reproduce, copy, modify, license, sell or disseminate in any manner any information obtained from this website. This website may contain inaccurate or incorrect information. Invention companies may make modifications to the content presented on this website at any time without notice. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and Invention companies as a result of use of this website or the existence of the Terms and Conditions of Use. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. Invention companies reserves the right to revise the Terms and Conditions and/or Privacy Policy at any time without notice by updating this posting. Use of any information or data provided by this website, without prior written permission by Invention companies, is expressly prohibited and may result in civil and/or criminal action. Violators will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible. Under no circumstances will Invention companies be liable for any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use or data, whether in an action of contract or in connection with the use or performance of information available from this website. Any action related to this website will be governed by Arizona law and controlling U.S. federal law. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Maricopa County, Arizona for all disputes arising out of or relating to this website.

Third Party Websites: This website contains links to other Third Party websites, which are not operated by Invention companies. These Third Party websites are not under the control of Invention companies and Invention companies is not responsible for the contents of any linked Third Party website or any link contained in a Third Party website. Invention companies provides these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Invention companies.

Disclaimer: The data that is provided by Invention companies is intended solely for informational purposes. Invention companies does not necessarily endorse or support any data provided by its affiliates/advertisers. Any products or services offered or sold by Invention companies affiliates/advertisers are the sole responsibility of the affiliates/advertisers and are not offered or supported by Invention companies. As Invention companies websites are solely an information resource, Invention companies is not responsible for the actual quality of any product or service offered by any iRelocation Network affiliates/advertisers that is received, including any expressed or implied warranties offered by such affiliates/advertisers. It is the individual customer's complete responsibility and obligation to independently assess the quality of any services or products that they purchase, and to make sure that these services or products meet the individual's needs. Users agree that Invention companies is not liable in any way for any damages that may occur from the use of current or former member's products or services, or for any errors or omissions that may appear on the Invention companies websites.

Copyright © Inventionleads.com 2023. All Rights Reserved. | [Privacy Policy](https://inventionleads.com/privacy)

×

Close

×

Close
